uk2.net 2007-12-22

# Terms & Conditions - Privacy Policy | UK2

## Information

  * When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and payment information such as credit card number and expiration date. 
  * We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide certain demographic information, such as age, gender, special interests, etc. You do not have to provide this type of information to use our service if you do not want to. 
  * If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your operating system, software and other technical matters. 
  * When you visit our website we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our website that you view. We may tie this information to the personally identifiable information we have about you. 
  * We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our website. See "What is a Cookie" below. We may tie this cookie to the personally identifiable information we have about you. 
  * When we send you an e-mail, we may include a marker that will allow to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed. 

## Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We will use your personally identifiable information only as follows:

  * For payment purposes and to provide customer support;
  * To announce special offers or provide other information from time to time via e-mail. We may also send e-mail announcing special offers by our third parties, but we will not provide the third parties with your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt out of future e-mails at any time by following the instructions included in the e-mail;
  * To improve our service and the marketing of our service. For example, we may use the information we gather from user surveys, demographic data, and web site visits to help us improve or target our website and customize your visit.

We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than:

  * A law enforcement or regulatory agency at their request; 
  * A person or company who acquires our business;
  * Third parties who perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing), subject to the third party agreeing with us that it will keep your personally identifiable information confidential;
  * To the parent, associated and subsidiary companies of UK-2 Group Ltd.
  * To our affiliates, or as otherwise needed to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of others. 

We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists. 

## Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may share aggregate statistical data about our customers with third parties, such as advertisers or suppliers. This aggregate statistical data will not identify you personally.

## Security of your Information

We store your personally identifiable information and payment information on a databases located in the UK, and in full compliance of the Data Protection Act. All data such as card numbers are encrypted and we will take reasonable security measures to protect your personal identifiable data in our databases.

## Children's Privacy

Our service is not available to persons under the age of 18, and we will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under the age of 18.

## What is a Cookie?

A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our website so that we may customise your visit.
